这首翻唱对30年代Cole Porter的原版
进行了一定改编
翻译，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源宋体 SemiBold
思源黑体 Medium
What ever happened to those good old days?
以前那些美好时光中的事物都经历了些什么
In olden days a glimpse of stocking
以前的日子看长筒袜的眼神
Was looked on as something shocking,
是认为长筒袜是不道德的憎恶眼神
Now, heaven knows,
现在的话 天知道人们在想啥
heaven knows,
天知道
Anything goes
随你们的便
学习音轨在简介中的原简介赞助页面中
Good authors too who once knew better words,
那些曾经会用好词的作家
Now only use four letter words writing prose,
现在只会用四个字母的单词来写散文了
writing prose
写散文
Anything Goes.
随你们的便
The world has gone mad today
现在的世界已经疯狂
And good's bad today,
好的变成坏的
And black's white today,
黑的都给洗白
And day's night today,
昼夜颠倒
When most guys today
而那些男性
That women prize today
最受女性欢迎的男性
Are just silly gigolos
都是些小鲜肉
So though I'm not a great romancer
虽然我不是一个很会讲故事的人
I know that you're bound to answer
我知道你们肯定会先回答
When I propose,
而不等我提议
I propose
我提议
Anything goes
随你们的便
When mothers pack and leave poor fathers
当母亲们收拾行李 离开她们的丈夫们
Behind they decide they'd rather be tennis pros,
只是因为她们更喜欢打网球
Anything goes
随你们的便
Just think of those shocks you got,
想想那些让你惊讶的东西
And those knocks you got,
让你震动的东西
And those blues you got
让你悲伤的东西
From that news you got,
从新闻中得知的消息
And those pains you got
让你痛苦的东西
If any brains you got
如果你还有脑子
From those little radios.
这些都来自那小小的收音机
So every night,
所以每天晚上
The set that's smart
一批时髦的人
Is indulging in nudist parties in studios,
沉溺于工作室里最赤裸裸的派对的时候
studios
工作室
Anything goes
随你们的便吧
随你们的便
They used to wear Victorian clothes
他们以前穿着维多利亚时代冠冕堂皇的服装
But now they all show silken hose
但现在全穿着丝袜
Heaven knows
天知道
Anything Goes
随你们的便